Krai...
Yes?
I think I want to fill a role
that our group is lacking.
Why's that?
If I do that, we could all
have fun being hunters...
Jeez.
I don't have a particularly strong body.
Then maybe it'll be a good fit for you.
Becoming an alchemist.
The thing with Sitri's Slime is
that the speed of its evolution,
the ability to adapt to its environment,
has been greatly improved.
But it's still a failure.
It is?
Don't worry.
I adjusted it so
it won't attack the two of us.
Oh.
So you and I are safe?
Yes.
Wait, only us?
Even if it could get out of
the metalium alloy capsule,
it couldn't get out of this safe because
of the dimensional misalignment.
Uh, Sitri?
The slime got out of the capsule and
escaped when you opened the safe.
Is that the right answer?
Huh?
The room has no vents or pipes.
Being a slime, it should still
instinctively prefer high humidity.
And so it escaped through this drain.
Is that the right answer?
Yeah, that's right.
So you're saying a slime that has the
power to destroy the entire capital
was oozing around this room?
I think I'm going to puke.
Please leave this matter to me.
Are you sure?
Yes.
And then, there's another matter...
Another matter?
We are now in the golden age
of the treasure hunters!
Amid the sparkling talent on
display in the capital of Zebrudia,
there was one man who stood
out amongst all others!
His name is Krai Andrey.
The White Wolf's Den.
Huh?
This is an epic tale
full of glory and agony,
of how he became renowned
for being the leader
of the strongest party he founded
with his childhood friends,
and also the master of the strongest clan!
If we don't do something,
the entire investigation team
will likely be wiped out.
What?!
For ranged attacks, hunters
naturally resort to magic.
But I deliberately chose the bow instead!
Episode 07
The Akashic Tower Wants to Experiment
"The Akashic Tower Wants to Experiment."
Let This Grieving Soul Retire
Nothing in the White Wolf's Den
treasure vault seems normal anymore.
Elite hunters from Steps and
the Association
have been dispatched in order
to conduct a large scale investigation.
In turn, the secret organization Akashic Tower
readies itself to deal a decisive blow.
Is a brutal clash between the two
factions inescapable fate?
And then there's our Krai Andrey,
who really doesn't want to get involved.
His ingenious scheme is to be
steadfast in not doing anything.
Is that really all right?
Good work, Sven.
Thanks.
How's it looking?
Doesn't look like anything's
happening right now.
Is anyone coming to take command?
I don't mind if people
do their own thing,
but we have so many of them...
Krai said to follow the
command of the Crosses.
Not surprised he isn't showing up,
but where's Liz?
I know she wanted to come.
Krai ended up commandeering her and Tino.
Looks like he's got a job
for them somewhere else.
That's good.
Would've been impossible to coordinate
anything with Stifled Shadow around.
You got that right.
All right, then.
Okay! Gather around!
Let's talk strategy!
Anyone here ever had a serious
battle against slimes?
No.
Nope.
Have not.
Never done that.
Are they even something
you can have a proper battle with?
I've stepped on some and
squashed them without noticing.
Did anyone bring anything
useful against slimes?
Slimes are weak against slashes.
My normal sword will do!
They're also weak against blunt weapons!
I've got my hammer!
They're weak against magic, too!
My magic flame can take
them out in one shot.
Or my wind magic.
I've brought this anti-slime spray.
It was only 700 gil, so I
have no idea if it works.
I'll crush them with my shield!
I guess it's not surprising.
Even civilians see slimes
as harmless creatures.
So telling us to be wary
of them is a bit much...
You're right.
Did he say anything else?
Just that it's not a normal slime.
Damn it.
Why does he always have to be
so stingy with information?
It's always the same thing...
This is stupid.
Let's hurry up and get back to exploring.
If you're so afraid of the slime,
we'll take care of it.
If it even appears, that is.
Uh-huh.
He doesn't get it.
That's too bad.
Wh-Why are you looking at me like that?!
You don't get it, do you?
Everybody thinks you'll
be the first to fall.
What did you say?
Just for the record.
I tried to stop you.
You got that?
Just don't die in vain.
Leave some clues.
We'll avenge you.
You're all freaking crazy!
Blindly believing the words of
some guy who's not even here!
Excuse me!
Yes? A question?
I'm an alchemist.
My name is Talia Wydman.
An alchemist?
I didn't know our clan had
an alchemist besides Sitri.
I was with Sitri in the clan's laboratory.
We were doing research on the
potential of slimes together.
Then do you know their weak points?
This is a potion Sitri
created that kills slimes.
It won't have an effect on anything else,
but if anything is related to them,
it'll most likely kill it, too.
The time has come.
Yes.
Your research is powerful.
With our preparations,
there is no chance of failure.
We're facing less than a hundred hunters,
and only a few even have second names.
It shouldn't be a problem
to eliminate them.
How do you intend to make your first move?
Right. First, I will...
Listen up!
We'll start taking control of the interior in parties.
Be meticulously aware of everything!
We'll use whistles to communicate.
If there's an emergency, or if you
discover something, make a sound!
Everybody who's not assigned to
the interior is on rescue duty!
Be on standby outside, and keep an
eye on the surrounding area as well!
Give it everything you've got and charge!
Run roughshod over them!
Leave your footsteps!
Let's all come back alive
and tell our dumbass master
that we eat these kinds
of trials for breakfast!
Only wolf knights, huh?
I didn't expect to find nothing at all.
Only the already reported fact
that the phantoms are stronger...
Has Krai's insight become clouded?
At this rate, if nothing happens...
It means that we were lucky.
If you hadn't given us useless orders,
this would have been over hours ago.
Save your complaints for after.
If you just got back stay put.
You better go pray to your precious master,
who couldn't even bother to show up!
Hey. Don't go off on your own.
Shut up!
I'm taking a leak!
Sheesh.
I don't know Krai very well,
but I know I trust you, Sven.
Then I guess I better stay worthy
of that and pray to our master.
Damn it.
This is so stupid.
Didn't expect Obsidian Cross to be
such a pack of spineless cowards.
Thousand Tricks, my ass. This is ridiculous.
If it were Ark Rodin, that'd be one thing,
but this guy's kicking back in the capital,
predicting what'll happen here?
What a joke.
Was that a wolf knight?
Is this really the right move?
We're up against close to a hundred hunters.
That experiment freak.
Just because she's our mentor's favorite...
She can barely even use magic!
"Whatever you do, don't fail,"
she said.
As if that needs to be said!
Let's get this forced transmogrification
using mana material over with.
Yes.
What the...
I'm a hunter!
Why you...
Damn it!
That hurts!
Why you...
You bastard!
Why... are you here...
Is Thousand Tricks behind this again?
He's not here!
All of this is coming from me!
I see. So Thousand Tricks isn't here, eh?
You!
What the hell are you doing?
Do it, Hos.
Do what?
The body of this phantom underwent
a forced transmogrification.
It will desire highly
concentrated mana material.
What?
Now, between us and you...
I wonder who has absorbed
more mana material.
This thing is bad news.
What is it?
That's the whistle.
You heard it?
That was one blow of the whistle!
Everyone on alert!
Call everyone back out!
It's outside!
What are we going to face?
Hey, where's Gein?
He hasn't come back yet.
What?
It's a monster!
Gein?
You... Your arm!
Thousand Tricks was telling the truth!
It's a slime!
A slime?
I've never seen a slime like that!
Don't stop moving!
It's slow to act.
Mages, keep it contained!
First, we stop it from advancing.
Henrik, help Gein!
Yes, sir!
Please let me see.
What happened?
These weird guys injected
something into a wolf knight.
Then it turned into slime.
Thousand Tricks' words were true.
Get back.
That's impossible.
It's unscathed?
Goddamn Krai.
How is this a slime?!
Screw you!
This can't be.
How are both physical and
magical attacks ineffective?
What should we do?
Well, just escaping in
the nick of time won't do.
We can't let this thing run loose.
Don't let it get close to you!
If it attacks you, focus on evading!
Let's box it in! It's slow!
Put everything you've got into this!
Talia!
I'll do it.
If it touches the liquid inside,
the slime should self-destruct. I think.
Got it.
Thank you!
Hey, you! This way!
It jumped?!
Sven!
Don't underestimate me.
There it is!
Die, freaking slime!
Damn it!
I knew it wasn't really a slime!
Screw you, Krai!
O-Oh, no...
Damn it!
That reminds me.
Krai did say it was something slime-like.
"Like"?!
He needs to quit thinking the Grievers are the
norm when they can brute-force anything!
How many times is he going
to almost get us killed?!
It nullifies magic.
Huh? Nullifies magic?!
Sitri?
What the hell are you doing here?
Krai told me things were probably
getting pretty bad here.
Krai.
Please believe in me and let me take charge!
Please.
Tremendous amounts of magic
swirl around its exterior,
forming a powerful force field.
That's what's deflecting your arrows
and nullifying other magic.
I haven't seen a phantom
this strong before,
not even in a level 8 treasure vault.
It is extremely interesting.
Its body is melting...?
The mana material composing the phantom is
forcibly being changed into magical power.
Which means...
Hey, Sitri!
It's trying to replenish its melted body
by absorbing additional mana material?
Is that why it's trying to eat me,
because I've absorbed more mana
material than anyone else here?
Poor thing.
This experiment is a failure.
It's too dangerous!
Fall back for now!
I appreciate the concern, Sven.
But how about this?
What?
There!
Please shoot it!
What did you throw?
Anti-mana metal.
Is it done?
Branch Manager Gark?
Why are you dressed like that?
He gave me a ride.
I can't run like my sister can.
What is all this?
Let me give you a proper explanation.
I have an idea about what this phenomenon
might be and who's pulling the strings.
She defeated the transmogrified
phantom that easily?!
Sitri Smart.
The one Sophia said was on our tail...
She managed to understand the nature
of the transmogrification potion?
The Akashic Tower?
You're saying they're conducting research
on how to control treasure vaults at will?
Impossible!
Noctus Cochlear... The Master of Mages,
was permanently banished.
There's no way he's in the empire!
I wasn't expecting you to believe me.
That's why I've been chasing after
the Master of Mages by myself.
There are already anomalies
occurring in the treasure vaults.
I assume the previous phantom was
a by-product of their experiments.
Uh, Sitri?
Talia!
Doesn't that mean they have some
sort of equipment underground?
Right.
Good thinking.
They would need large-scale
equipment to carry this out.
That's the heart of his research.
Which means that they are
already prepared for battle.
We'll interrogate the
mages that Gein captured.
I don't think this will be the only
monster of that type we encounter.
But if you have that stick
you threw earlier—
I'm sorry.
That was all of my anti-mana metal.
I never imagined we'd face
something like this.
Krai didn't tell you?
Tell me what?
Damn him. Not again.
But we can do this.
I'll do the analysis.
It shouldn't be too difficult
with this many hunters.
I'm not Krai, but I'll give it my best.
I cannot fight at all,
so please lend me your strength.
She's such a steadfast person.
You mean Sitri?
"I cannot fight at all"...
I would never be able to say that.
She's pretty strong for being weak.
Huh?
Watch out.
Don't get taken in by her.
Meaning what?
She says she's weak.
So she thinks she can do
anything and get away with it.
Using whatever means necessary
is natural for her.
As far as I'm concerned,
she's just as much a monster
as every other Griever.
Hey, hey, Si could die
if she's all by herself.
She's as weak as can be,
and she said Killiam was under
maintenance right now, too.
I'm really worried about her!
So, come on!
Absolutely not.
But why?!
Even Liz's request doesn't make him budge.
With his iron will, he still refuses to move.
I wanna go! I wanna go!
Is that really all right?!
You had no screen time at all!
I wanna go! I wanna go! I wanna go!
Our Krai Andrey!
Please tune in again next time?
I wanna go!
Shut up!
Welcome to the White Wolf's Den!
From Obsidian Cross, live at the White Wolf's Den
You still got it?
Obsidian Cross!
You still got it!
Pick up your weapons.
And stand up!
We're all going, we're all going. Yeah!
Yeah!
Let's go!
Okay, listen up!
Let This Grieving Soul...
...Retire!
Episode 08
I Want to Rush In When It's Over
What happened to Krai?!
"I Want to Rush In When It's Over."
I discovered this when I was
still called "The Prodigy."
The Nature of Mana Material and the
Potential of Treasure Vaults...
The author is the Master of Mages,
Noctus Cochlear.
At that stage, what was written there
was little more than a pipe dream.
Still, I instinctively knew that
it was something extremely dangerous—
something that could potentially
encroach on the domain of gods.